are already houses welcome back and in this video I'm going to show you how to
已经 欢迎回到家里了 这个视频我将告诉 你如何
sort custom objects using multiple different attributes it's actually going
使用多个排序自定义对象 它实际上正在发生的不同属性
to be really useful but before we begin I need to ask you guys something
在我们开始之前真的很有用 我 需要问 你们一些事情
have you ever heard the term I ship something I was actually texting a girl
你有没有听说过我这个词 我正在 发短信 的女孩
uh yesterday and she goes I ship yada yada yada and I go you ship something what's that mean was that like a typo or
呃 昨天她去了 我的船 yada 亚达亚达和我去你的 东西 这是什么意思， 就像一个错字 或
what the heck are you talking about she goes now that's like a saying now when
究竟发生了什么， 你说 什么 ，她 现在这就像现在说的那样
you say I ship something it means you really like something and I thought she
你说我发货意味着你 真的很喜欢 ，我想她
was just messing with me but then I looked it up online and apparently that's like a saying now so if anyone
只是搞砸了我，但后来我 在网上看起来很明显 这就像现在说的那样，如果有人的话
ever heard before then let me know maybe I'm just like a way out of the loop um
之前听说过， 也许 让我 知道 我只是一个 摆脱循环的方式嗯
for those of you who do say that don't anymore because it sounds stupid but I
对于那些说不这样 做的人 了 ，因为它听起来很愚蠢 ，但 我
don't know learn something new every day so anyways go ahead and type from
不知道 每天都在学习新东西 所以无论如何继续并输入
operator import item get ur figure it's a minute in this video now much work
运营商导入项目得到你的数字 在这个视频中的一分钟现在很多工作
learning some actual Python now and what I'm going to do is I'm going to show you
现在学习一些实际的Python 和什么 我会做的就是我要 告诉 你
guys how to sort a custom this is actually more often than not going to be
你们如何排序的自定义，这 是 实际上往往比往往更多
a bunch of custom objects but for this tutorial I just have a bunch of
一堆自定义对象，但为此 教程中，我只是有一堆
dictionaries in here so each object is of course has multiple attributes these
这里的词典就是每个对象都是 当然这些有多个属性
ones just have a first name and last name and I'm going to show you guys how
那些 只是有一个姓氏 和 名字，我要告诉你们怎么样
to sort these and then I'm going to show you guys why sorting them that way is a
对 这些 进行排序 ，然后我将 展示 你们为什么这样排序他们是一个
problem and how to do it properly so we want to go ahead and sort these by I
问题以及如何正确地做到这一点 ， 所以我们 想继续 和我整理这些
don't know first name why not so I'm going to write X in sorted all right
不知道 名字为什么不，所以我 打算将X写入排序好的
first thing of course what do you want to sort users so anything we can really
首先当然是你想要什么 对用户进行排序， 以便我们能够做到
users and what attribute do you want to sort by so instead of just saying okay
用户以及您想要的属性 这样排序， 而 不仅仅是说好的
sort these by whatever default method you have we know that we can actually
通过任何默认 方法排序这些 你知道我们可以
access the attributes so we can sort by either first name or last name pretty
访问属性，以便我们可以排序 名字或 姓氏 漂亮
cool how do we do that the key or the thing that we want to sort by equals
我们怎么做那个关键还是关键 我们想要按等于排序的东西
item getter and this is just like attribute getter essentially F&A
项目吸气器，这就像 属性getter基本上是F＆A
cool cool everyone's going to be sorted by their first name let's just go ahead
酷酷的每个人都要排序 以他们的名字让我们继续吧
and print this out and all right Amanda Burnie Tom looking good wait a minute
打印出来，好吧阿曼达 Burnie Tom 看起来很好等一下
look at this right here see whenever it's sorted all the Tom's it didn't
看看这里就 在这里看看 它排序了所有的 汤姆 它没有
really sort it in a true alphabetical order because it has Tom Roberts then Tom Williams and then Tom Jones I
真的按字母顺序排序 订购， 因为它有汤姆罗伯茨 汤姆威廉姆斯 然后汤姆琼斯 我
mean if this was a true alphabetical sort it would be Jones then Roberts then
这意味着如果这是一个真正的字母 然后 是琼斯 然后是罗伯茨
Williams so I mean go back here and let me go
威廉姆斯 所以我的意思是回到这里让我离开
ahead and sort by L name and that should fix that problem what the heck
提前并按L名称排序，那应该是 解决那个 问题到底是什么
look at this it's ordered by last names but whenever sorted by you know this
看看这是按姓氏排序的 但每当你知道这一点
group Robert says it has Bucky Tom and Amanda
小组罗伯特说它有Bucky Tom和 阿曼达
so I mean Amanda should be first and then Bucky and then Tom so how the heck
所以我的意思是阿曼达应该是第一个 然后Bucky 然后汤姆如此哎
do we sort it in true alphabetic order where let's say we want to sort by first
我们按照真正的字母顺序对其进行排序 让我们说我们想先排序
names but then those subgroup of let's say Williams is we want to sort those
名字， 但然后是那个子组 威廉姆斯说我们想要那些
further by last name so what we can do is this
更进一步的姓氏所以我们能做什么 这是
I'm just go ahead and print out a little separator line and I'm just doing that
我只是继续打印一下 分隔线，我只是 这样做
because I'm going to post all the source code on my github page so if you guys
因为 我要发布所有的来源 我的github页面上的代码，所以如果你们
want to sort by one attribute I'll keep that there too but what I want to do is
我希望按一个属性排序 那也是我想要做的
I want to pretty much do the same thing before I'm going to sort users but now
我想做同样的事情 在我打算 对用户进行排序之前
for Mikey come on autocomplete I was good I don't I get angry like when I
对于Mikey 来说， 我是 自动完成的 好的，我不会像 我 一样生气
just don't type in one like symbol and I'm like oh my god autocomplete can you
只是不要输入象符号和 我喜欢哦，我的神自动完成你可以
not just type the rest of my code for me all these cool features for i DES they
不只是为我输入我的其余代码 所有这些酷的功能为 他们的 DES
just made me incredibly lazy but you know I don't know whatever all right so
只是让我变得非常懒惰但是你 知道我不知道什么 没事如此
just like before we're going to sort by item getter but instead of just having one attribute in here such as f name
就像我们 要排序 之前一样 物品吸气剂，而 不仅仅是 这里有 一个 属性，比如f name
says that didn't give us the desired results we can actually throw in another
说没有给我们所希望的 结果我们实际上可以扔进另一个
attribute so what we're saying right here is go ahead get all of these items
所以我们所说的正确 这里继续获取所有这些 项目
and first sort them by their four name now once you have all these items
并首先按他们的 四个排序 一旦你拥有所有这些 项目， 现在就命名
sorted by their first names look at the individual groups of names and then sort
按名字排序 看看 各个名称组然后排序
those further by last name really awesome so now let's go ahead and print
真的是姓氏 太棒了所以现在 让我们继续打印
this out so this one was default one and look at the Tom's in the first one
这个， 所以这个是默认的一个 看看第一个汤姆的
Roberts Williams and Jones that's not right the second one however it sorts all of the objects by their first name
罗伯特·威廉姆斯和琼斯这 不是 对第二个， 但它排序 所有对象的名字
and then once it has sorted it goes further and sorts them by last name so
然后一旦它已经排序它去了 进一步按姓氏对它们进行排序
now this is a true alphabetical sort where everything even the subgroups are
现在这是一个真正的字母排序 即使是小组也是如此
sorted properly so a lot more useful especially whenever you're trying to you
正确排序， 因此 更有用 特别是 每当你想 你
know like make a database and find stuff a lot quicker so there you go so yeah
知道像创建数据库并找到东西 更快，所以 你去，所以是的
again I'm probably going to go look at some more terms on Urban Dictionary and
再次 我 可能会去看看 关于“城市词典”的更多术语
yeah maybe you guys want study some more Python so actually I'll probably just make another video so I'll see you guys
是的，也许你们想要学习更多 Python实际上我可能只是 再拍视频，所以我会看到你们
then
然后